Shyam rao Pagidimarri

Hyderabad, Telangana, 500097 +919030719369 raoshyam90@gmail.com

Career Objective

To be a part of an organization where I can put my skills and efforts for the development of company and in return gain experience and acquaintance of people. Assistant Manager fluent in various areas of corporate business with top-notch organization and technology skills. Devoted work ethic and leadership to influence team building. Resourceful in cutting company costs and helping to boost customer and employee workplace satisfaction.

Academic Qualification

Jawaharlal Nehru University 60% Bachelor of Engineering	Graduated May 2016
Narayana Junior College 75% Intermediate	Graduated May 2012
Sri Krishnaveni Talent School 70% SSC	Graduated May 2010

Employment History

Aryabhatta Techno solutions.

Assistant Manager Marketing

March 2018 - Present

- Arranged team meetings and coordinate with departments to help with communication and team building
- Create and maintain scheduling of employees to execute fairness of hours and vacations
- Document and implement changes to policies and ensure compliance by keeping policy notebooks up to date and relevant
- Responsible for assisting in budget development and monthly reports for department
- Maximized department efficiency by streamlining documentation procedures to ensure completion of deadline projects
- Assisted with training new hires, orienting to department and current staff and managers

Sambav EHR pvt ltd.

August 2017 - February 2018

Business development executive

- To build and maintain strong relationships with clients.
- Demonstrating & Presenting the product or service to clients.
- Follow-ups to clients through call, email.
- Identifying and establishing new business.
- Maintaining accurate & detailed records.
- Negotiating contracts and packages.
- Organizing appointments and meetings with clients to promote company products as per the company strategy.
- Responsible for developing strong relationship with clients.

• Accountable for identification and segregation of potential market segments.

KPDI Industries Ltd

January 2017 - July 2017

Business development executive

- Develop new business via telephone and mass communication such as email and social media to introduce the Montage solution and identify appropriate buyers within the target market.
- Follow up on leads and conduct research to identify potential prospects
- Building strong network and connection in the industry through cold calling and e-mail campaigning
- Introducing company's services among decision makers.
- Understanding and identifying prospect's requirements for Market Research and fixing appointments for our front-line sales.
- Build and cultivate prospect relationships by initiating communications and conducting follow-up communications in order to move opportunities through the sales funnel

Achievements

- In KDPI Industries I Got tie up with SAMIL Company(Shriram Automall India Limited), Worked For some companies in all segments like Manufacturing, FMCG, Hospitals, Hospitality, etc...
- In Sambav We worked with Doctors, Hospitals, conducting the Health camps.

Hobbies and interests

Writing ,learning,Cooking,Camping,